Guide to the Hartt School faculty collection ARCH063
University of Hartford Archives & Special Collections
Hartt School faculty collection
1898-2013
University of Hartford Archives & Special Collections
Hartt School
University of Hartford. Archives and Special Collections
ARCH063
13.29 Linear Feet (31 containers)
Conditions Governing Access
The collection is open to all researchers. However, files from the Document Records Series requires prior review from the University Archivist to determine if there is a need to restrict access to any, or all records, in the file in accordance to the Archives' restriction policy concerning personnel records.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains material related to the activities of administrators and faculty of the Hartt School. These materials include programs, correspondence, writings, compositions, newspaper clippings, photographs, and faculty data.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged into four series: I. Document records, II. Photographs, III. Compositions, and IV. Duplicates.
Photographs; Hartt School -- Faculty; University of Hartford -- Faculty; Scores; Composition (Music); Hartt School; Julius Hartt School of Music; Hartt College of Music
- Document records, 1898-2013
  Conditions Governing Access
  Files from the Document Records Series requires prior review from the University Archivist to determine if there is a need to restrict access to any, or all records, in the file in accordance to the Archives' restriction policy concerning personnel records.
  Scope and Contents
  This series consists of publicity materials, concert/event programs, correspondence, and faculty data.
  - Akon, Alfred (Alfred Cohn), 1931-1963 (Box Document Records 1)
  - Alexander, Carlos, 1941-1947 (Box Document Records 1)
  - Anderson, Everett, 1946-1947 (Box Document Records 1)
  - Aronson, Stanley, 1979-1997 (Box Document Records 1)
  - Ashens, Robert, 1990 (Box Document Records 1)
  - Babineau, Ninette, 1954-1979 (Box Document Records 1)
  - Badge, Ahlene (Mrs. Peck), 1939-1956 (Box Document Records 1)
  - Baker, David, 1967 (Box Document Records 1)
  - Baker, Jules, 1949-1958 (Box Document Records 1)
  - Baker, Julius, 1949-1951 (Box Document Records 1)
  - Balogh, Emo, 1952-1953 (Box Document Records 1)
  - Balsam, Artur, 1958 (Box Document Records 1)
  - Banat, Gabriel, 1955-1962 (Box Document Records 1)
  - Beatman, Joseph W., Undated (Box Document Records 1)
  - Beeler, Walter, Undated (Box Document Records 1)
  - Bellsion, Simeon, 1946-1953 (Box Document Records 1)
  - Benstock, Seymour, 1949-1961 (Box Document Records 1)
  - Bergner, Carl, 1948-1950 (Box Document Records 1)
  - Berman, Melvin, 1948-1962 (Box Document Records 1)
  - Bertsche, Samuel, 1947-1957 (Box Document Records 2)
  - Bilotti, Anton, 1923-1947 (Box Document Records 2)
  - Blewett, Marie, 1955-1962 (Box Document Records 2)
  - Bliem, William, 1957-1959 (Box Document Records 2)
  - Bodenhorn, Aaron, 1898 (Box Document Records 2)
  - Bonacini, Renato, 1963-1974 (Box Document Records 2)
  - Brawley, Robert S., 1955-1969 (Box Document Records 2)
  - Broadhead, Edward, 1947-1975 (Box Document Records 2)
  - Broadhead, Helen, 1955-1957 (Box Document Records 2)
  - Bronne, Ariana`, Undated (Box Document Records 2)
  - Bronstein, Raphael, 1928; 1981; 1984; Undated (Box Document Records 2)
  - Brynley, David, 1950 (Box Document Records 2)
  - Buechner, Alan, 1967 (Box Document Records 2)
  - Bunnell, Lyman B., 1941-1953 (Box Document Records 2)
  - Burige, Susan, 1960-1964; Undated (Box Document Records 2)
  - Castro, Bridget de Moura, 1996 (Box Document Records 2)
  - Castro, Luiz de Moura (De Moura, Castro), 1983; 2000; 2011 (Box Document Records 2)
  - Cavin, Suzanne, 1965 (Box Document Records 2)
  - Chakerion, Charles, 1948-1956; Undated (Box Document Records 2)
  - Chatzy, Herbert, 1972 (Box Document Records 3)
  - Cheney, Timothy, 1947-1987 (Box Document Records 3, Box Shared Book Tray 2, Object 0207301236403)
    Includes a copy of: Cheney, Timothy. Beyond the Wheel. (Portland, Maine: House of Falmouth, Inc., 1959).
  - Clark, Walter Houston, 1952-1957 (Box Document Records 3)
  - Cloutier, Norman, 1955 (Box Document Records 3)
  - Cochrane, Walter, 1967 (Box Document Records 3)
  - Cogswell, Walter, 1950-1967 (Box Document Records 3)
  - Conci, Noretta, 1961 (Box Document Records 3)
  - Cote, Collette P., 1961 (Box Document Records 3)
  - Crotty, Howard T., 1950 (Box Document Records 3)
  - Csornay, Richard, 1950-1951 (Box Document Records 3)
  - Dadman, Royal, 1937-1964 (Box Document Records 3)
  - Davis, Steve, 2000; 2012 (Box Document Records 3)
  - Deming, Howard, 1952-1960 (Box Document Records 3)
  - De Pasquale, Joseph, 1948-1951 (Box Document Records 3)
  - Dewing, Nancy, 1966 (Box Document Records 3)
  - Diemente, Edward, 1960-1991 (Box Document Records 3)
  - Dinerstein, Norman, 1980; Undated (Box Document Records 3)
  - Dipillo, Cesidia, 1943-1965 (Box Document Records 3)
  - Doney, John, 1961-1965; 1973 (Box Document Records 3)
  - Dorsey, Ruth, 1947; 1952 (Box Document Records 3)
  - Douglass, Geraldine, 1956-1959 (Box Document Records 4)
  - Downs, Thomas, 1957-1965 (Box Document Records 4)
  - Einstein, Alfred, 1940-1980 (Box Document Records 4)
  - Ellison, Esther N., 1939 (Box Document Records 4)
  - Epstein, Alvin, 1950; 1952; 1968 (Box Document Records 4)
  - Farkas, Alexander, 1978 (Box Document Records 4)
  - Farley, William, 1977; 1987 (Box Document Records 4)
  - Farrell, Eileen, 1979; 1981; Undated (Box Document Records 4)
  - Feierabend, John, 1991; 2001; 2008; Undated (Box Document Records 4)
  - Ferrante, John, 1953-1960 (Box Document Records 4)
  - Fidlar, Dorothy, 1950-1984 (Box Document Records 4)
  - Fidlar, Wilfred, 1992 (Box Document Records 4)
  - Fieldman, Bernice Beatrix, 1950-1951 (Box Document Records 4)
  - Finckel, David, 1995 (Box Document Records 4)
  - Flint, Peter, 1991 (Box Document Records 4)
  - Fonte, Henry, 1998; 2004 (Box Document Records 4)
  - Forbes-Davis, Joan, 1966-1968 (Box Document Records 4)
  - Foster, Richard, 1989 (Box Document Records 4)
  - Fox, Davis, 1985; Undated (Box Document Records 4)
  - France, Herbert, 1947-1953 (Box Document Records 4)
  - Freeman, Stanley, 1941-2001 (Box Document Records 4)
  - Friedberg, Carl, 1951-1952 (Box Document Records 5)
  - Gamble, Claire, Undated (Box Document Records 5)
  - Garbousova, Raya, 1971; 1982; Undated (Box Document Records 5)
  - Gaudet, Laura, 1998; undated (Box Document Records 5)
  - Gelbloom, Gerald, 1959-1961 (Box Document Records 5)
  - George, Earl, 1948, 1952; 1952 (Box Document Records 5)
  - Giannin, Vittorio, 1939-1952 (Box Document Records 5)
  - Gigliotti, Charles, Undated (Box Document Records 5)
  - Girard, Dale, 1996 (Box Document Records 5)
  - Girard, Jane H., 1996; undated (Box Document Records 5)
  - Gittleman, Neil, Undated (Box Document Records 5)
  - Glazier, Joan Leopold, Undated (Box Document Records 5)
  - Goldie, Don, 1995, undated (Box Document Records 5)
  - Goldstein, William D., 1962; 1986 (Box Document Records 5)
  - Goltzer, Harold, 1949-1953 (Box Document Records 5)
  - Gomberg, Harold, 1948-1953 (Box Document Records 5)
  - Goodrich, Kathlene, 2003-2004; undated (Box Document Records 5)
  - Gordon, Jacques, 1933; undated (Box Document Records 5)
  - Gordon, Ray and Helen, 1969; undated (Box Document Records 5)
  - Graf, Herbert, 1942-1944 (Box Document Records 5)
  - Gray, Kevin, 2013 (Box Document Records 5)
  - Greenblatt, Hamon, 1994-1996 (Box Document Records 5)
  - Greehouse, Berard, 1961-1970 (Box Document Records 5)
  - Gresh, Theodore, 1955-1957; undated (Box Document Records 5)
  - Groff, Frank, 1948-2003 (Box Document Records 5)
  - Grossman, Helen, 1969; undated (Box Document Records 5)
  - Gryc, Steve, 2004, undated (Box Document Records 5)
  - Guilet, Daniel, 1945-1949; undated (Box Document Records 5)
  - Gustafson, John M., 1967; undated (Box Document Records 5)
  - Hadcock, Peter, 1967-1968 (Box Document Records 5)
  - Hailey, Christopher, Undated (Box Document Records 5)
  - Halligan, William, 1947-1952; 2002 (Box Document Records 5)
  - Hanson, Raymond, 1948-1965 (Box Document Records 6)
  - Hayes, Barbara, 1951-1957 (Box Document Records 6)
  - Haynes, Lowell B., 1953-1957 (Box Document Records 6)
  - Hering, Sigmund, 1947-1952 (Box Document Records 6)
  - Henkmann, Virginia, 1964; undated (Box Document Records 6)
  - Hess, Robert, 1991 (Box Document Records 6)
  - Hintz, Elmer, 1945-1955 (Box Document Records 6)
  - Hoffman, Allen, 1969; undated (Box Document Records 6)
  - Holcolm, Al Dee, undated (Box Document Records 6)
  - Holmes, Heloise, 1992 (Box Document Records 6)
  - Holz, John, Undated (Box Document Records 6)
  - Hubbard, Helen, 1965-1985 (Box Document Records 6)
  - Hubert, Marcel, 1942-1948 (Box Document Records 6)
  - Hurwitz, Issac D., 1961 (Box Document Records 6)
  - Iadone, Joseph, 1959-1972 (Box Document Records 6)
  - Inagraham, Paul, 1979; 1984 (Box Document Records 6)
  - Jackson, Douglas, Undated (Box Document Records 6)
  - Jackson, Javon, 2013 (Box Document Records 6)
  - Jacobi, Frank, 1939-1956 (Box Document Records 7)
  - Jacobs, James, 1997; 2000; undated (Box Document Records 7)
  - Jacobson, Cecile, 1955-1967 (Box Document Records 7)
  - Jacobson, Gordon, 1986 (Box Document Records 7)
  - Jamanis, Michael and Fran, 1976; 1990 (Box Document Records 7)
  - Jarratt, Howard, 1947-1948 (Box Document Records 7)
  - Johannesen, Grant, 1988 (Box Document Records 7)
  - Johnson, Eleanor, 1941-1957 (Box Document Records 7)
  - Johnson, Gilbert, 1949-1959 (Box Document Records 7)
  - Jordan, James, 1986-1989 (Box Document Records 7)
  - Karas, Joza, 1934, 1955-1984 (Box Document Records 7)
  - Karr, Gary, 1979-1989 (Box Document Records 7)
  - Kaschmann, Trude, 1958-1961 (Box Document Records 7)
  - Kasper, Timothy, 2004 (Box Document Records 7)
  - Katahn, Enid, 1952-1958 (Box Document Records 7)
  - Katahn, Martin, 1952-1955 (Box Document Records 7)
  - Katz, David, 1984, 2004-2005 (Box Document Records 7)
  - Kelsy, John, 1960-1968 (Box Document Records 7)
  - Kim, Suk Soon, 1969 (Box Document Records 7)
  - Klippstatter, Kurt, 1978-1990 (Box Document Records 7)
  - Klock, Lynn, 1978-1980 (Box Document Records 7)
  - Kolb, Barbara, 1977-1990 (Box Document Records 8)
  - Kopman, Israel, 1950-1962 (Box Document Records 8)
  - Koret, Cantor Arthur, 1990; undated (Box Document Records 8)
  - Korn, Mitchell, 1989-1993 (Box Document Records 8)
  - Koscielny, Anne, 1972-1990 (Box Document Records 8)
  - Kroll, William, 1955-1963; undated (Box Document Records 8)
  - Kugelman, Alice, 1965-1968 (Box Document Records 8)
  - Laderoute, Joseph, 1963-1965; undated (Box Document Records 8)
  - LaGace, Kenneth, 1972-1975; undated (Box Document Records 8)
  - Lagrutta, Aldo, 1989-1990 (Box Document Records 8)
  - Landerman, Sally, 1998; 2008; 2010 (Box Document Records 8)
  - Landowska, Wanda, 1952; 1959; 1999 (Box Document Records 8)
  - Lane, Mary, 1947-1957 (Box Document Records 8)
  - Langston, Amy, 1929-1951 (Box Document Records 8)
  - Langton, Stephen, 1978 (Box Document Records 8)
  - Larsen, Henry, 1952-2001 (Box Document Records 8)
    Includes a copy of: Larsen, Henry. Lecture on Improvising. (West Hartford, CT: s.n., 1972).
  - LaVerne, Andy, 2012 (Box Document Records 8)
  - Leiss, Yolanda, 1949-1957 (Box Document Records 8)
  - Lenom, Clement, 1942-1949 (Box Document Records 8)
  - Lepak, Alexander, 1955-1993 (Box Document Records 8, Box Document Records 9)
  - Lewis, Brenda, 1973-1993 (Box Document Records 9)
  - Licht, Kenneth, 1965-1969 (Box Document Records 9)
  - Lieberman, Milton, 1949-1957 (Box Document Records 9)
  - Lischner, Rose, 1938-1955 (Box Document Records 9)
  - Loebell, Victoria Ketterer, Undated (Box Document Records 9)
  - Lohmann, Ladger, 1987-1989 (Box Document Records 9)
  - Long, Grayce, 1960-1995 (Box Document Records 9)
  - Lopatnikoff, Nikolai, 1942-1945 (Box Document Records 9)
  - Lucarelli, Bert, 1971-2001 (Box Document Records 9)
  - Lurie, Bernard, 1970 (Box Document Records 9)
  - Lyman, Peggy, 2002-2005 (Box Document Records 9)
  - Lynn, Enid, Undated (Box Document Records 9)
  - Macbride, David, 1990 (Box Document Records 9)
  - MacDonald, Ann, 1947-1952 (Box Document Records 9)
  - Mack, Gerald, 1986 (Box Document Records 9)
  - Mack, Joan, 1949-1953 (Box Document Records 9)
  - Mack, Mary Nixon, 2012 (Box Document Records 9)
  - Mackown, Mildred, 1996 Dec (Box Document Records 9)
  - Magg, Fritz, 1961-1990 (Box Document Records 9)
  - Maison, Rene, 1946 (Box Document Records 9)
  - Malbin, Elaine, 1986-1991 (Box Document Records 9)
  - Margulis, Michael, 1967-1968 (Box Document Records 9)
  - Marijosius, Vytautas, 1954-1996 (Box Document Records 9, Box Document Records 10)
  - Mark, Penelope-Burridge, 1970 (Box Document Records 10)
  - Martin, Gene, 1955-1958 (Box Document Records 10)
  - Marx, Josef, 1960 (Box Document Records 10)
  - Mase, Raymond, 1982-1986 (Box Document Records 10)
  - Mattingly, James, 1950-1999 (Box Document Records 10)
  - Mattran, Donald, 1971-1979 (Box Document Records 10)
  - Mayes, Samuel, 1951-1953 (Box Document Records 10)
  - Maxwell, Robert, 1939 (Box Document Records 10)
  - Maxym, Stephen, Undated (Box Document Records 10)
  - McIlroy, William, 1991 Feb (Box Document Records 10)
  - McKim, William, 1953-1965 (Box Document Records 10)
  - McKonly, Curtis, 1987 (Box Document Records 10)
  - McKown, Marguerite, 1951-1956 (Box Document Records 10)
  - Means, Louisa, 1964 (Box Document Records 10)
  - Mears, Diane, 1986 (Box Document Records 10)
  - Meier, Laura, 1945-1954 (Box Document Records 10)
  - Meier, Scott, Undated (Box Document Records 10)
  - Mende, Rose, 1950-1979 (Box Document Records 10)
  - Menuhin, Jeremy, 1988 (Box Document Records 10)
  - Mercer, Virginia, 1941-1947 (Box Document Records 10)
  - Metcalf, William, 1969-1988 (Box Document Records 10)
  - Metcalfe, Scott, 2002, circa 2007 (Box Document Records 10)
  - Meyers, Robert, 1964-1967 (Box Document Records 10)
  - Michna, Marienka, 1941-1956 (Box Document Records 10)
  - Miller, Charalene, Undated (Box Document Records 10)
  - Miller, Edward, 1967-1968 (Box Document Records 10)
  - Miller, Patrick, 1983-1994 (Box Document Records 11)
  - Mirovitch, Alfred, 1966-1987 (Box Document Records 11)
  - Mishkind, Abraham, 1966-1987 (Box Document Records 11)
  - Mitchell, James, 1959-1960 (Box Document Records 11)
  - Mizelle, Diana, 1987 (Box Document Records 11)
  - Montoni, Raymond, 1947-1952 (Box Document Records 11)
  - Moore, Kermit, 1951-1953 (Box Document Records 11)
  - Moreland, Donald, 1967 (Box Document Records 11)
  - Morrison, Watson, 1969-2007 (Box Document Records 11)
  - Moses, Frederic "Fritz", 2009 (Box Document Records 11)
  - Mowe, Homer, 1954-1958 (Box Document Records 11)
  - Mueter, John, 1977 (Box Document Records 11)
  - Muller, Dana, 1988 (Box Document Records 11)
  - Mulready, Joseph, 1976 (Box Document Records 11)
  - Murtha, Roger, 2007, undated (Box Document Records 11)
  - Nackowsky, Jane, 1947-1949 (Box Document Records 11)
  - Nadeau, Lise, 1955-1961 (Box Document Records 11)
  - Nagel, Robert, 1967, 1979 (Box Document Records 11)
  - Neaman, Yfrah, 1985-1989 (Box Document Records 11)
  - Nickrenz, Scott, 1983-1987 (Box Document Records 11)
  - Nikolais, Alwin, 1969, 1993 (Box Document Records 11)
  - Norville, Hubert, 1941 (Box Document Records 11)
  - Notley, Norman, 1949 (Box Document Records 11)
  - Oakley, Paul, Undated (Box Document Records 11)
  - Opperman, Kalmen, Undated (Box Document Records 11, Box Shared Book Tray 2, Object 0207303177324)
    Includes a copy of: Opperman, Kalmen, comp. Repertory of the Clarinet. (New York: Colombo, 1960).
  - O'Riley, Christopher, 1983-1988 (Box Document Records 11)
  - Ostrander, Allen, 1974 (Box Document Records 11)
  - Otis, Cynthia, 1950-1959 (Box Document Records 11)
  - Owens, Dewey, 1958-1960 (Box Document Records 11)
  - Palardy, Theresa Maria, 1952-1960 (Box Document Records 11)
  - Pappoutsakis, James, 1957-1958 (Box Document Records 11)
  - Palmer, Charles, 1978 (Box Document Records 11)
  - Parnas, Leslie, 1977-1982 (Box Document Records 11)
  - Peck, Sally, Undated (Box Document Records 11)
  - Pellettieri, Louis, 1962-1988 (Box Document Records 12)
  - Perry, Pamela, 1990 (Box Document Records 12)
  - Perry, Stephen, Undated (Box Document Records 12)
  - Pertis, Peter, 1983-1987 (Box Document Records 12)
  - Pierce, Ilona, 1999-2000 (Box Document Records 12)
  - Polanski, Louis, 1952 (Box Document Records 12)
  - Poyana, Raphael Antonio, 1954-1959 (Box Document Records 12)
  - Pruett, Jerome, 1998 (Box Document Records 12)
  - Putsche, Thomas, 1985-1989 (Box Document Records 12)
  - Rabine, Eugene, 1970 (Box Document Records 12)
  - Rascher, Sigurd, 1939-1940 (Box Document Records 12)
  - Racuhe, Anthony, 1990 (Box Document Records 12)
  - Reese, Kimberly, Undated (Box Document Records 12)
  - Restout, Denises, 2004 (Box Document Records 12)
  - Rewinsky, Leo, 1955-1960 (Box Document Records 12)
  - Ridolfi, Robert, 1952-1953 (Box Document Records 12)
  - Riofrancos, Osvaldo, 1972 (Box Document Records 12)
  - Rizzi, Victoriana, 1965-1978 (Box Document Records 12)
  - Robb, Madelyn, 1941-1960 (Box Document Records 12)
  - Robinson, Leo, 1952-1976 (Box Document Records 12)
  - Rochberg, George, 1989 (Box Document Records 12)
  - Routch, Robert, 1988 (Box Document Records 12)
  - Rose, Leonard, 1951-1960 (Box Document Records 13)
  - Rosenblith, Eric, 1985-1995 (Box Document Records 13)
  - Ross, John, Undated (Box Document Records 13)
  - Rostropovich, Mstislav Leopoldovich, 1971-1981 (Box Document Records 13)
  - Rottner, Leslie, 1972-1974 (Box Document Records 13)
  - Rozie, Richard (Rick) Jr. and Lee Maurice (Mixashawn), 2000 (Volume 0207303177332)
    Is a copy of: Emidy, Marjorie. The Emidy Family: Joseph Antonio Emidy and Jane (Jenefer) Hutchins of Cornwall, England and some descendants. (Viroqua, WI: M.A. Emidy, 2000).
  - Rusack, Richard, 1998 (Box Document Records 13)
  - Russo, Charles, Undated (Box Document Records 13)
  - Ryerson, Ali, 2001 (Box Document Records 13)
  - Savino, Frank, 1986 (Box Document Records 13)
  - Sayao, Bidu, 1957-1964 (Box Document Records 13)
  - Sayevich, Ben, 1985 (Box Document Records 13)
  - Scafarello, Margaret, 1928-1952 (Box Document Records 13)
  - Scelba, Anthony, 1994 (Box Document Records 13)
  - Schaffer, Robert, 1949-1971 (Box Document Records 13)
  - Schapiro, Maxim, 1943-1949 (Box Document Records 13)
  - Schawago, Myron, 1983 (Box Document Records 13)
  - Schleicher, Donald, 1984 (Box Document Records 13)
  - Scholes, Kim, 1986-1987 (Box Document Records 13)
  - Schorr, Friedrich, 1941-1988 (Box Document Records 13)
  - Schorr, Virginia E., 1963-1992 (Box Document Records 13)
  - Schwager, Myron, 1987 (Box Document Records 13)
  - Schuller, Gunther, 1985-1989 (Box Document Records 13)
  - Seeber, Leonard, 1946-1952 (Box Document Records 13)
  - Segal, Rubin, 1930-1955 (Box Document Records 13, Box Document Records 14)
  - Sellars, James, 1984-1986 (Box Document Records 14)
  - Senz, Regina, 1949 (Box Document Records 14)
  - Setzer, Philip, 1998 (Box Document Records 14)
  - Shelton, Lucy, 1980-1984 (Box Document Records 14)
  - Shuler, Scott, 1990 (Box Document Records 14)
  - Shules, Scott C., Circa 1990 (Box Document Records 14)
  - Silva, Luigi, 1957-1961 (Box Document Records 14)
  - Silverherz, Dorothy, 1960 (Box Document Records 14)
  - Simpson, Claire, 1949 (Box Document Records 14)
  - Singleton, Kenneth, 1979-1981 (Box Document Records 14)
  - Sinta, Donald, 1982 (Box Document Records 14)
  - Small, Rosemary, 1986-1990 (Box Document Records 14)
  - Smith, Bryan R., 2005, 2008 (Box Document Records 14)
  - Smith, David, 1970-1985 (Box Document Records 14)
  - Smith, David L., 1979 (Box Document Records 14)
  - Smith, Gordon, 1958-1959 (Box Document Records 14)
  - Smith, Julia, 1936-1974 (Box Document Records 14, Box Shared Book Tray 3, Object 0207303177373)
    Includes a copy of: Smith, Julia, Ruth Shafer, and Dorothy Pease, eds. Music for Youth: Book Six. (Julia Smith, 1936).
  - Snyder, Kerala, 1981-1987; undated (Box Document Records 14)
  - Soifer, Joseph, 1985 (Box Document Records 14)
  - Sollenberger, Elizabeth, 1972 (Box Document Records 14)
  - Southworth, Virginia, 1986-1987 (Box Document Records 14)
  - Spekter, Edythe, 1959-1967 (Box Document Records 14)
  - Spence, George, 1955 (Box Document Records 14)
  - Stanton, Mary, 1975-1980 (Box Document Records 15)
  - Steele, George, 1948-1949 (Box Document Records 15)
  - Steffan, Sofia, 1972-1986 (Box Document Records 15)
  - Stein, Elliott, 1957 (Box Document Records 15)
  - Stern, Issac, 1980-1985 (Box Document Records 15)
  - Stern, Mitchell, 1992, 2001 (Box Document Records 15)
  - Stoll, Fred, 1948 (Box Document Records 15)
  - Stroud, James, 1958 (Box Document Records 15)
  - Sturtevant, Ruth, 1972-1973 (Box Document Records 15)
  - Swallow, John, 1969-1973 (Box Document Records 15)
  - Sydeman, William, 1958-1967 (Box Document Records 15)
  - Terry, Kenton, 1943-1945 (Box Document Records 15)
  - Tierney, John, 1990 (Box Document Records 15)
  - Tolo, Leland, 1982-2003 (Box Document Records 15)
  - Tomat, Jean, 1961-1980 (Box Document Records 15)
  - Trachtenberg, Stephen, 1977-1978 (Box Document Records 15)
  - Treger, Charles, 1971-1985 (Box Document Records 15)
  - Treggor, Philip, 1967, 2004 (Box Document Records 15)
  - Trisler, Joyce, 1956 (Box Document Records 15)
  - Uppman, Theodor, Undated (Box Document Records 15)
  - Urban, Bella, 1955-1957 (Box Document Records 15)
  - Urban, Virginia, 1946-2001 (Box Document Records 15, Box Document Records 16)
  - Vallecillo, Irma, Circa 1990 (Box Document Records 16)
  - Veri, Frances, 1964-1966 (Box Document Records 16)
  - Verrilli, Norma, 1950-1952 (Box Document Records 16)
  - Von, Wurtzler, 1964-1967 (Box Document Records 16)
  - Walker, John, 1962-1963 (Box Document Records 16)
  - Wallace, Lenzy, 1988 (Box Document Records 16)
  - Wason, Robert, 197 (Box Document Records 16)
  - Watson, David, 2007-2008 (Box Document Records 16)
  - Weaver, Constance, 1947-1952 (Box Document Records 16)
  - Weigl, Karl, 1937 (Box Document Records 16)
  - Weiner, Mildred, 1953 (Box Document Records 16)
  - Weis, Theodore, 1955 (Box Document Records 16)
  - Weld, Sara, 1964 (Box Document Records 16)
  - Wells, David, 1963-1982 (Box Document Records 16)
  - Wells, George Ross, 1947-1956 (Box Document Records 16, Box Shared Book Tray 2, Object 0207303177357, Object 0207303177365)
    Includes a copy of:
    Wells, George Ross. The Art of Being a Person. (New York: D. Appleton-Century, Inc., 1939).
    Wells, George Ross. Individuality and Social Restraint. (New York: D. Appleton-Century, Inc., 1929).
  - Werner, Donald, 1988 (Box Document Records 16)
  - Westerman, Kenneth, 1949 (Box Document Records 16)
  - Westover, Harold, 1968 (Box Document Records 16)
  - White, Dolores, 1956-1957; 2010 (Box Document Records 16)
  - White, Donald, 1955-1957; 2010 (Box Document Records 17)
  - Willens, Joyce, 1953-1956 (Box Document Records 17)
  - Willet, William, 1973-2000 (Box Document Records 17)
  - Willheim, Imanuel, 1953-2000 (Box Document Records 17)
  - Winograd, Arthur, 1989 (Box Document Records 17)
  - Winograd, Betty, 1987 (Box Document Records 17)
  - Wion, John, 1982-2007 (Box Document Records 17)
  - Wright, Alfred, 1951 (Box Document Records 17)
  - Young, Gene, 1994-1995 (Box Document Records 17)
  - Youse, Stuart, 2000-2001 (Box Document Records 17)
  - Zei, John, 1977-2000 (Box Document Records 17)
  - Zolas, Edward, 1964-1965 (Box Document Records 17)
- Photographs, 1930-2004
  - Adelaide, Bishop, Undated (Box Photographs 1)
  - Akon, Alfred (Alfred Cohn), Circa 1962 - Circa 1963; Undated (Box Photographs 1, Box Shared Small Oversized 2)